odigger.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy | oDigger

Last updated 01/01/2015

We realize that you care about the use of your information, and we respect your concerns. We have put strict policies into place to ensure that the privacy of your personal information is protected while still enabling you to make use of the services provided by ODigger.com.

This Privacy Pledge outlines the steps we've taken to ensure that you have a great experience at ODigger.com, and also provides details on how we treat any personal information you may submit to us or third parties.

**Other Information Collection and Use**

Like many other web-based service providers ODigger.com collects limited non-personally identifiable information provided by your browser as you use our website and services. This is done in order to provide the best possible services to you and our other users. This non-personally identifiable information may include (but is not limited to) IP address, browser type, time and date of use, and any activity performed while on our Website or using our services. We may also place and/or read cookies on your computer to help us identify whether you have visited our site in the past so we can customize our services and your experience. Please note that this information is gathered solely during the time you are visiting the ODigger.com web site. ODigger.com takes note of the web site that referred you to our web site, but otherwise does not gather information about web pages you have visited before or after visiting our web site.

Additionally, we may capture click-stream data on some of our partner's websites, limited to the activity involved within our website and with the completion of offers listed on our website. This information is used to monitor the performance of our site and partners.

We will collect and use personal information about you to respond to your request for products and services offered through this website. We will also collect information in order to notify you about products, services, and other opportunities we think will be of interest to you. Information we gather and/or you provide directly or indirectly to our website may be shared with third parties.

**The information we collect may be from the following sources:**

  * **1-** Information provided by you in connection with obtaining a certain product or service offered by one our business partners. 
  * **2-** Information you provide us when you register to receive communications from us (such as your email address). 
  * **3-** Information you provide us through telephone and web based surveys, customer service correspondence, and general feedback. 

**Marketing Email Options**

You may register to receive communications from us directly on our website. Upon registering and creating/signing up for a user account on oDigger, we will periodically send you newsletters and other e-mails with offers and promotions. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by sending an email to [support@odigger.com](mailto:support@odigger.com) (You may also opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails).

**Third Party Link**

ODigger.com connects consumers with third party links. When you visit websites to which ODigger.com links, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain certain services or products through a third party site, the data collected by the third party is governed by that third party's privacy policy. A third party site will also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and clear gifs. These partners will protect your information against distribution, loss, theft, and misuse. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

**Disclosures Under Law**

We make every effort to preserve user privacy. We cooperate with legal authorities when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on LendALot.

**Children**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes to this Privacy Pledge**

ODigger.com may update or modify this Privacy Pledge from time to time. If there are material changes to this Privacy Pledge or in how ODigger.com will use your personal information, we will post such changes here. You will be notified if any of the material changes that affect the use of your personal information and asked to opt-in to the new use of your personal information. If you do not agree with the changes to how your information will be used, please do not continue to use this website.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the ODigger.com Privacy Pledge. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use any of the ODigger.com site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our website to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our Privacy Pledge will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Pledge.

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, you should first contact us at: [support@odigger.com](mailto:support@odigger.com)

oDigger.com is owned and operated by Zen Networks LLC
